Guide to the Trinity College of Arts and Sciences, Office of the Dean records, 1911-2006 UA.25.02.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Container List
  - Sarah P. Duke Gardens, 1974-1975 (Box 27)
  - Schedule Committee, 1966-1973 (Box 27)
  - Scholarships, 1972-1974 (Box 27)
  - Security, 1966-1971 (Box 27)
  - Seminars, 1967-1970 (Box 27)
  - SHARE: Experimental Living Project - Wilson, 1966-1974 (Box 27)
  - J. Raymond Smith Athletic Scholarship Fund, 1974 (Box 27)
  - Sororities: General, 1967-1974 (Box 27)
  - South Atlantic Quarterly, 1972-1973 (Box 27)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools, 1967-1973 (Box 27)
  - Special Events Office, 1973 (Box 27)
  - Staff Meeting: Associate Dean of TCAS, 1972-1974 (Box 27)
  - Staff Meeting: Bi-weekly, Kruger's, 1972-1973 (Box 27)
  - Staff: Outside, 1973-1974 (Box 27)
  - Staff Potential, 1964-1974 (Box 27)
  - Statistics, University Committee on, 1974 (Box 27)
  - Stein: Joseph, Baird, 1955-1975 (Box 27)
  - Ann Barbour Stow Memorial Scholarship, 1972-1974 (Box 27)
  - Streaking: Spring 1974 (Box 27)
  - Student Advisory Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 27)
  - Student Affairs Office, 1972-1974 (Box 27)
  - Student Aid Fund, 1969-1974 (Box 27)
  - Student Discussion Groups, 1969-1970 (Box 27)
  - Student Fee and Allocation Procedure: ASDU, 1969-1974 (Box 27)
  - Student Financial Aid, 1967-1973 RESTRICTED (Box 27)
  - Student Grievances, 1971 (Box 27)
  - Student Health, 1969-1972 (Box 27)
  - Student Health Advisory Committee, 1967-1970 (Box 27)
  - Student Loan List, 1972 (Box 27)
  - Student Leave of Absence, 1966-1968 (Box 27)
  - Student Participation in University Committees, 1967-1970 (Box 27)
  - Student Records, 1963-1971 (Box 27)
  - Student Residential Life Study Committee, 1968-1971 (Box 27)
  - Student Services, 1972-1973 (Box 27)
  - Student-Teacher Evaluation, 1970-1974 (Box 27)
  - Student Teaching Program, 1967-1970 (Box 28)
  - Student Union, 1966-1972 (Box 28)
  - Study Abroad, 1966-1973 (Box 28)
  - Summer Session, 1962-1974 (Box 28)
  - Summer Session for Freshmen, 1963-1974 (Box 28)
  - Summer Session: General, 1971-1972 (Box 28)
  - Symposiums, 1966-1972 (Box 28)
  - Teaching Council: Undergraduate, 1973-1974 (Box 28)
  - Telephone Information, 1968-1974 (Box 28)
  - Testing Students, 1969-1974 (Box 28)
  - Traffic Commission, 1966-1970 (Box 28)
  - Transfer Students, 1972-1974 (Box 28)
  - Transportation, Buses and Private Cars, 1961-1974 (Box 28)
  - TCAS Scholarship Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 28)
  - Trinity Deans: Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1967-1972 (Box 28)
  - Trustees, 1967-1974 RESTRICTED (Box 28)
  - Trustee List, 1967-1974 RESTRICTED (Box 28)
  - Trustee Meetings, 1965-1974 RESTRICTED (Box 28)
  - Tuition Deferred Plan, 1971-1974 (Box 28)
  - Tuition Fees, Refunding Procedures, etc., 1962-1975 (Box 28)
  - University Judicial Board, 1969-1974 RESTRICTED (Box 28)
  - Undergraduate Judicial Board, 1969-1974 RESTRICTED (Box 28)
  - Undergraduate Judicial Board Precedent File, 1971 RESTRICED (Box 28)
  - Undergraduate Judicial Board Precedent File, 1971 RESTRICTED (Box 28)
  - Union: Duke University, 1971-1974 (Box 28)
  - University: Academic Council, 1972-1974 (Box 28)
  - University Faculty, 1968-1973 (Box 28)
  - University: Indenture of Trust (Box 28)
  - University Judiciary Committee, 1968-1969 RESTRICTED (Box 28)
  - University Planning Commission, 1969-1973 (Box 29)
  - University Planning: Undergraduate Academic Programs, 1969-1973 (Box 29)
  - University Planning, 1969-1973 (Box 29)
  - University Planning: Faculty Development, 1969-1973 (Box 29)
  - University Planning Committee: Graduate Academic Programs Subcommittee, 1969- 1973 (Box 29)
  - University Planning Committee, 1969-1973 (Box 29)
  - Urban Fellowship Program, 1971-1972 (Box 29)
  - Urban Fellowship Program, 1971-1972 (Box 29)
  - Vacation: Staff, 1973-1974 (Box 29)
  - Video Tape Project, 1973-1974 (Box 29)
  - Visitation: Social Regulation Change, 1972 (Box 29)
  - Vitae, 1972-1973 (Box 29)
  - Watson Committee Report, 1969 (Box 29)
  - West Campus Community Council, WCCC, 1969-1971 (Box 29)
  - White House Fellows, 1972 (Box 29)
  - Winchester Excavation Committee, 1966 (Box 29)
  - Women's College Memorial Scholarship Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 29)
  - Women Members Faculty, 1967-1972 (Box 29)
  - Women's Programs, 1971-1973 (Box 29)
  - Woodrow Wilson National Fellowship Foundation, 1962-1968 (Box 29)
  - Work Study Program, 1968-1974 (Box 29)
  - A Better Chance, 1975-1977 (Box 30)
  - Academic Council, 1977-1979 (Box 30)
  - Academic Council, 1974-1976 (Box 30)
  - Acceleration, Patterns of December and September Completion, 1977 (Box 30)
  - Admissions, 1974-1979 (Box 30)
  - Advising Center, 1974-1979 (Box 30)
  - Advising in the Health Professions, 1973-1978 (Box 30)
  - Afro-American Studies, 1972-1980 (Box 30)
  - Afro-American Studies Minutes, 1975-1976 (Box 30)
  - Alumni Affairs, 1965-1979 (Box 30)
  - American Studies, 1978 (Box 31)
  - American Council on Education, 1974-1978 (Box 31)
  - American Council on Education Survey, 1974-1977 (Box 31)
  - Anthropology Department, 1974-1979 (Box 31)
  - Art Department, 1974-1979 (Box 31)
  - Associate Dean, 1974-1979 (Box 31)
  - Associated Students of Duke University, ASDU, 1979 (Box 31)
  - ASDU Legislature Minutes, 1974-1978 (Box 31)
  - ASDU, 1974-1978 (Box 31)
  - Association of African Students, 1976 (Box 31)
  - Association of American Colleges, 1977-1979 (Box 31)
  - Association of American Universities, 1974-1975 (Box 31)
  - Audio-Visual Committee Report, 1976-1978 (Box 31)
  - Audio Visual Program, 1975-1978 (Box 31)
  - Applicants - Edward H. Benenson Awards in Art History, 1979 (Box 31)
  - Benenson Awards, 1977-1978 (Box 31)
  - John O. Blackburn, 1972-1976 (Box 32)
  - Botany Department, 1974-1979 (Box 32)
  - Dean Virginia Bryan, 1975-1979 (Box 32)
  - Bulletin Information, 1972-1979 (Box 32)
  - Bunting Fellowship, 1979 (Box 32)
  - Business and Finance Self-Study, 1976 (Box 32)
  - Cable Television, 1976-1977 (Box 32)
  - Career Advisors, 1975-1977 (Box 32)
  - Career Counseling, Ad Hoc Committee on, 1977-1980 (Box 32)
  - Career Development and Continuing Education, 1974-1977 (Box 32)
  - Career Planning, 1975-1978 (Box 32)
  - Center for the Study of the Presidency, 1977-1978 (Box 32)
  - Chemistry Department, 1973-1979 (Box 32)
  - Classical Studies Department, 1976-1979 (Box 32)
  - Commencement, 1975-1980 (Box 32)
  - Commonwealth Program, 1975-1976 (Box 32)
  - Community Environment Education through Durham, 1976 (Box 32)
  - Computer Science Department, 1974-1979 (Box 32)
  - Consortium for Faculty Exchange, 1974 (Box 32)
  - Continuing Education, 1976-1979 (Box 32)
  - Continuing Education, 1974-1975 (Box 33)
  - Counseling Center, 1974-1979 (Box 33)
  - Counseling Services, Ad Hoc Committee on, 1974-1977 (Box 33)
  - Cuba Exchange Program, 1979 (Box 33)
  - Cultural Affairs Office, 1975-1976 (Box 33)
  - Dean's Advisory Committee, undated (Box 33)
  - Dean's Council, 1972-1980 (Box 33)
  - Dean, Trinity College, 1973-1979 (Box 33)
  - Dean's Staff, 1975-1979 (Box 33)
  - Dean's Staff Minutes, 1974-1979 (Box 33)
  - Directors of Undergraduate Studies, 1972-1980 (Box 33)
  - Distinguished Professor's Seminars, 1964-1979 (Box 33)
  - Douthat, James, 1974-1975 (Box 33)
  - Drama, 1977-1979 (Box 33)
  - Drama, 1974-1976 (Box 34)
  - Duke Endowment Awards, 1978-1979 (Box 34)
  - Duke Endowment Leaves - Applications, 1977 (Box 34)
  - Duke Endowment Leaves, 1976-1978 (Box 34)
  - East Campus Xerox, 1974 (Box 34)
  - Economics Department, 1975-1979 (Box 34)
  - Education, 1979 (Box 34)
  - Education: Report "Teacher Education at Duke University", 1979 (Box 34)
  - Education Development, Institute of, 1977 (Box 34)
  - Education Department, 1975-1979 (Box 34)
  - Educational Facilities Committee, 1974-1978 (Box 34)
  - Educational Goals, 1977 (Box 34)
  - Educational and Progress Special Committee Minutes, 1978-1979 (Box 34)
  - Educational Policy Program Special Committee, 1979 (Box 34)
  - Educational Policy Program Special Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 34)
  - Educational Policy and Curriculum Reform, 1976-1979 (Box 34)
  - Educational Testing Service, 1974 (Box 34)
  - Emergencies: Student, 1975 (Box 34)
  - School of Engineering, 1974-1976 (Box 34)
  - English Department, 1974-1979 (Box 34)
  - Environmental Center, 1977-1978 (Box 34)
  - Epoch Campaign, 1972-1975 (Box 34)
  - Epworth Inn, 1974-1978 (Box 34)
  - Equal Opportunity, 1979-1980 (Box 34)
  - Equal Opportunity, 1975-1978 (Box 35)
  - Expeditor Group, 1975-1979 (Box 35)
  - Faculty: General, 1976-1977 (Box 35)
  - Faculty Newsletter, 1981-1982 (Box 35)
  - Faculty Review of Academic Departments, 1979 (Box 35)
  - Kilgo Federation, 1974 (Box 35)
  - Federations, 1974-1979 (Box 35)
  - Financial Aid, 1974-1979 (Box 35)
  - Financial Aid Appeals Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 35)
  - Financial Aid Review Committee, Study Abroad, 1975 (Box 35)
  - Financial Report: Duke University, 1976 (Box 35)
  - Fine Arts Study Commission (Box 35)
  - Free University, 1933-1975 (Box 35)
  - Freewater Film Society, 1972-1976 (Box 35)
  - Freshman Composition Review Committee, 1974-1976 (Box 35)
  - Funding, 1978-1979 (Box 35)
  - Future Possibilities: Personnel, 1977-1979 (Box 35)
  - Geology Department, 1974-1977 (Box 35)
  - German Department, 1974-1979 (Box 35)
  - Goals, 1976 (Box 35)
  - Government Program, 1975 (Box 36)
  - Graduation Lists, 1974-1978 (Box 36)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration, 1974-1979 (Box 36)
  - Graduation List, 1977-1978 (Box 36)
  - Health Administration (Box 36)
  - Hew Grant, 1976-1978 (Box 36)
  - Special Services for the Disadvantaged, 1973-1976 (Box 36)
  - Higher Education and National Affairs, 1975-1979 (Box 36)
  - History Department, 1971-1979 (Box 36)
  - Housing, 1974-1979 (Box 36)
  - Human Sexuality Course, 1973-1974 (Box 36)
  - Institute of the Arts, 1976-1980 (Box 36)
  - Institute of European Studies, 1973-1978 (Box 37)
  - Institute of Policy Sciences and Public Affairs, 1971-1976 (Box 37)
  - Institute of Policy Sciences Advisory Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
  - Institutes/Workshops, 1974 (Box 37)
  - Intercollegiate Press Bulletins, 1975-1976 (Box 37)
  - Interdisciplinary Major in Business, 1978 (Box 37)
  - International Studies, 1979 (Box 37)
  - International Studies, 1973-1978 (Box 37)
  - Internship Program, undated (Box 37)
  - Jantz Collection, 1975 (Box 37)
  - Judicial Board, 1974-1978 (Box 37)
  - Kreps, Juanita, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
  - Liberal Arts Education, 1977-1980 (Box 37)
  - Long-Range Planning Documentation, 1977-1979 (Box 37)
  - MacAnderson Scholarship Fund, 1975-1979 (Box 37)
  - Marine Laboratory, 1977-1979 (Box 37)
  - Mathematics Department, 1973-1979 (Box 37)
  - Mexico, 1974-1976 (Box 37)
  - Minority Affairs, 1977-1978 (Box 37)
  - Minority Affairs, 1972-1976 (Box 38)
  - Music Department, 1975-1979 (Box 38)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1974-1979 (Box 38)
  - NSF Programs (Box 38)
  - Opportunity Courses: Film Courses, 1974-1979 (Box 38)
  - Personnel, 1974-1977 (Box 38)
  - Philosophy Department, 1973-1979 (Box 38)
  - Physical Education, 1974-1979 (Box 38)
  - Physics Department, 1975-1979 (Box 38)
  - Pilot Advising System, 1979 (Box 38)
  - Placement Services, 1974-1979 (Box 38)
  - Political Science, 1972-1980 (Box 38)
  - President, 1974-1978 (Box 38)
  - Project Wild, 1976-1978 (Box 38)
  - Promotion and Tenure Committee, 1972-1979 (Box 38)
  - Provost, 1979 (Box 38)
  - Provost, 1972-1978 (Box 39)
  - PSMSE, The Program to Strengthen Medical Science Education, 1976-1979 (Box 39)
  - Psychology Department, 1975-1980 (Box 39)
  - Psychological Services, 1974-1975 (Box 39)
  - Public Policy Sciences, 1976-1979 (Box 39)
  - Pye, Chancellor Kenneth, 1976-1977 (Box 39)
  - Readmissions, 1974 (Box 39)
  - Religion Department, 1974-1979 (Box 39)
  - Romance Language Department, 1971-1979 (Box 39)
  - Salaries, 1975-1979 (Box 39)
  - Sarah P. Duke Gardens, 1978-1979 (Box 39)
  - Search Committee Policy, 1975-1976 (Box 39)
  - Self-Study: Trinity College of Arts and Sciences, 1976 (Box 39)
  - Seminar in Science, Society and Human Values, undated (Box 39)
  - SGA Federations, 1976-1977 (Box 39)
  - Shaefer Proposal, 1976-1977 (Box 39)
  - SHARE: Wilson House, 1972-1979 (Box 39)
  - Slavic Department, 1976-1979 (Box 39)
  - Sociology Department, 1975-1979 (Box 39)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools, 1974-1976 (Box 39)
  - Speeches, 1974-1979 (Box 39)
  - Statistics, 1970-1979 (Box 39)
  - Student Affairs, 1974-1979 (Box 40)
  - Student Health, 1975-1976 (Box 40)
  - Student Marshals, 1975-1976 (Box 40)
  - Student Mental Health (Box 40)
  - Student Projects and Reports, 1977-1978 (Box 40)
  - Students, 1974-1977 (Box 40)
  - Student Teaching, 1974 (Box 40)
  - Summer Planning Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 40)
  - Summer Session, 1975-1977 (Box 40)
  - Summer Theater, 1974-1976 (Box 40)
  - Summer Transitional Program, 1972-1978 (Box 40)
  - Evaluation of STP, Committee on, 1979 (Box 40)
  - Surveys by Students, 1974-1979 (Box 40)
  - Teacher-Course Evaluation, 1973-1977 (Box 40)
  - Teacher-Course Evaluation, 1973-1976 (Box 40)
  - Teacher Education, 1974 (Box 40)
  - Towne House, 1976 (Box 40)
  - Transfer Students, 1975-1976 (Box 40)
  - Triangle World Affairs Center, 1979 (Box 40)
  - Trustees, 1974-1978 (Box 41)
  - Trustees List, 1974-1979 (Box 41)
  - University Marshal, 1973-1979 (Box 41)
  - Undergraduate Teaching, 1974 (Box 41)
  - University Union, 1974-1978 (Box 41)
  - Video Proposal, 1975-1976 (Box 41)
  - Vienna Program, 1972-1978 (Box 41)
  - Visiting Student Policy, 1974 (Box 41)
  - Woodlands - Whitewater Institute, 1976 (Box 41)
  - Writing and Composition Program, 1976-1977 (Box 41)
  - WP-WF Proposal, 1974-1975 (Box 41)
  - X-Rated Films, 1976-1977 (Box 41)
  - YM-YWCA, 1974-1975 (Box 41)
  - Zoology, 1970-1979 (Box 41)
  - Executive Committee: UFCAS, 1976-1978 (Box 41)
  - Executive Committee: UFCAS, 1967-1976 (Box 42)
  - UFCAS Representative, 1974-1979 (Box 42)
  - UFCAS: Committees, 1969-1979 (Box 42)
  - UFCAS: Roster, 1969-1970, 1975-1976 (Box 42)
  - UFCAS Bylaws, 1971 (Box 42)
  - UFCAS: Articles of Organization, 1962-1971 (Box 42)
  - UFCAS: Academic Standards Committee, 1960-1976 (Box 42)
  - Admissions and Financial Aid, Committee on, 1969-1978 (Box 42)
  - Athletics Committee, 1971-1975 (Box 42)
  - Advising Committee, 1971-1975 (Box 42)
  - Advising Committee, 1966-1978 (Box 43)
  - Course Committee: UFCAS, 1962-1977 (Box 43)
  - Curriculum Committee: UFCAS, 1964-1978 (Box 43)
  - Curriculum Committee: UFCAS, 1969 (Box 44)
  - Curriculum Committee: UFCAS, 1969 (Box 44)
  - Honors Committee, 1969-1975 (Box 44)
  - Program II Committee, 1969-1974 (Box 44)
  - Residential Life Committee, 1969-1977 (Box 44)
  - Study Abroad Committee, 1963-1977 (Box 44)
  - Study Abroad Committee: UFCAS, 1974-1975 (Box 44)
  - UFCAS Reorganization, 1962-1971 (Box 45)
  - UFCAS: Miscellaneous, 1968-1971 (Box 45)
  - UFCAS: Historical Materials, 1951-1965 (Box 45)
  - Black Studies Committee, 1969-1974 (Box 45)
  - Directors of Undergraduate Studies, 1968-1972 (Box 45)
  - Officer Education Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 45)
  - Policy Subcommittee, 1964-1971 (Box 45)
  - Advisory Committee, Institute of Policy Sciences and Public Affairs, 1972-1973 (Box 45)
  - Departmental Advising System for Declared Majors - Final, 1983 (Box 45)
  - Departmental Advising System for Declared Majors - Draft, 1983 (Box 45)
  - Final Epstein Report, 1983 (Box 45)
  - UFCAS Committee on Advising, 1982-1983 (Box 45)
  - Questionnaire for Departmental Advisers, Student Advising System, 1982 (Box 45)
  - Draft Report on the Academic Advising System for Declared Majors, 1982 (Box 45)
  - Advising, 1982-1983 (Box 45)
  - Undergraduate Faculty Council of Arts, 1977-1978 (Box 45)
  - Transmittal Letter and List of People Who Received the Advising Report, 1983 (Box 45)
  - Draft Copy of the Report on the Departmental Advising System for Declared Majors, 1983 (Box 46)
  - Originals: Questionnaire - Chairman, 1982 (Box 46)
  - Questionnaire to Department Chairman, 1982 (Box 46)
  - Questionnaire to Major Advisers, 1982 (Box 46)
  - Questionnaire to Students and Telephone Survey, Student Advising System, 1982 (Box 46)
  - Faculty - Advising Survey, 1982 (Box 46)
  - Advising Questionnaire Telephone Survey, Random Sampling Materials, 1982 (Box 46)
  - Telephone Advising Survey, 1982 (Box 46)
  - Student Advising Survey, 1982 (Box 46)
  - ASDU Pre-Program Advising Report, 1978 (Box 46)
  - Course Committee Historical, 1958-1979 (Box 46)
  - Deaning, 1974 (Box 46)
  - Honors: Assembly and Statistics, 1963-1974 RESTRICTED (Box 46)
  - Undergraduate Bulletin: General, 1974-1982 (Box 46)
  - Freshmen: Summer Session, 1972-1976 (Box 46)
  - Women's College Scholarship Committee, 1959-1977 (Box 46)
  - Alice M. Baldwin Constitution, 1963-1976 (Box 46)
  - Sandals Constitution, 1973-1974 (Box 46)
  - Delta Delta Delta Constitution, circa 1968 (Box 46)
  - Woman's College Scholarship Committee: Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 46)
  - Subsequent Committee Rulings on Alice Baldwin Constitution, 1974 (Box 46)
  - Evelyn Barnes Constitution, undated (Box 46)
  - PanHellenic Constitution, 1967-1974 (Box 46)
  - Woman's College Scholarship Committee: Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 46)
  - TCAS Scholarships, 1973-1976 (Box 46)
  - Delta Delta Delta Applicants [scholarship], 1968-1972 (Box 46)
  - Evelyn Barnes Applicants [scholarship], 1969 (Box 46)
  - PanHellenic-Sandals Applicants [scholarship], 1969 (Box 46)
  - Letters to Winners of Women's College Scholarships, 1971-1972 (Box 46)
  - Alice M. Baldwin Applicants [scholarship], 1969 (Box 46)
  - Scholarships, 1970-1974 (Box 46)
  - Women's Scholarship Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 46)
  - N. C. Memorial Scholarship Application: Returned, 1972 RESTRICTED (Box 46)
  - Application, undated (Box 46)
  - TCAS Pre-Major Advising Center, 1985 (Box 46)
  - Academic Council, 1983 (Box 46)
  - Academic Council, 1980-1982 (Box 47)
  - Academic Facilities Office, 1981-1983 (Box 47)
  - ACE Fellow: Dr. Edward Cohen, 1982 (Box 47)
  - ACE Fellow: Debra Stewart, 1982 (Box 47)
  - Admissions, 1980-1983 (Box 47)
  - Admissions and Financial Aid Personnel, 1971-1978 (Box 47)
  - Admissions, Financial Aid, Academic Records and System Review, 1982 (Box 47)
  - Financial Aid: Undergraduate, 1979 (Box 47)
  - Admissions: Undergraduate, 1982 (Box 47)
  - Advising Center, 1980-1981 (Box 47)
  - Advising: General, 1979-1983 (Box 47)
  - Advising in Health Professions, 1982-1983 (Box 47)
  - Academic Affairs Committee: Board of Trustees, 1975-1981 RESTRICTED (Box 47)
  - Academic Affairs Committee: Board of Trustees, 1982 RESTRICTED (Box 47)
  - Academic Affairs Committee: Board of Trustees, 1983 RESTRICTED (Box 47)
  - Advising in Health Professions, 1979-1981 (Box 47)
  - Aerospace Studies, 1980-1982 (Box 47)
  - Afro-American Studies, 1980-1982 (Box 48)
  - Afro-American Studies Information, 1971-1980 (Box 48)
  - Aging and Human Development, Center for Study of, 1983 (Box 48)
  - Aging, Center for, 1980-1982 (Box 48)
  - Alumni Affairs, 1980-1983 (Box 48)
  - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1980-1983 (Box 48)
  - American Council on Education, 1980-1982 (Box 48)
  - Angier B. Duke, 1982-1983 (Box 49)
  - Anthropology, 1980-1983 (Box 49)
  - Art, 1980-1983 (Box 49)
  - University Art and History Preservation Committee, 1981 (Box 49)
  - Art Museum, 1980-1983 (Box 49)
  - Arts and Sciences Campaign, 1980-1983 (Box 49)
  - ASDU, Associated Students of Duke University, 1983 (Box 50)
  - ASDU, 1980-1982 (Box 50)
  - ASDU Legislation, 1980-1982 (Box 50)
  - Asian Pacific Studies Institute, 1980-1983 (Box 50)
  - Baldwin Federation, 1974-1980 (Box 50)
  - Asian Pacific Studies Institute Budget, Directorship and Minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 50)
  - Asian Pacific Studies Institute Roster and General Information, 1980-1981 (Box 50)
  - Associate Dean, 1980-1982 (Box 50)
  - Association of American Colleges, 1980-1981 (Box 50)
  - Association of American Universities, 1980-1982 (Box 50)
  - Athletic Department, 1971-1981 (Box 50)
  - Audio-Visual Committee, 1976-1983 (Box 50)
  - Beinecke Undergraduate Scholarship Program, 1976-1982 (Box 50)
  - Benenson Awards: General Correspondence, 1976-1980 (Box 50)
  - Benenson Awards, 1981-1983 (Box 50)
  - Benenson Awards: General Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 50)
  - Mary Duke Biddle Foundation, 1980-1983 (Box 50)
  - Biomedical Research Support Grants, 1982-1983 (Box 50)
  - Biomedical Research Support Grants, 1981 (Box 51)
  - Blackburn Festival, 1980 (Box 51)
  - Dr. Colin Blaydon, 1981-1982 (Box 51)
  - Botany, 1980-1982 (Box 51)
  - Dean Virginia Bryan, 1980-1981 (Box 51)
  - Bulletin Information, 1980-1982 (Box 51)
  - Bunting Fellowship, 1980-1982 (Box 51)
  - Business and Finance, 1972-1982 (Box 51)
  - Canadian Studies, 1980-1982 (Box 51)
  - CAPS, 1977-1980 (Box 51)
  - Career Planning, 1979-1981 (Box 51)
  - Chairmen's Council: Agenda and Minutes, 1983 (Box 51)
  - Chairmen's Council: Agenda and Minutes, 1980-1982 (Box 52)
  - Chemistry, 1982-1983 (Box 52)
  - Chemistry Department, 1981 (Box 52)
  - Chemistry, 1980 (Box 52)
  - China Exchange Program, 1982-1983 (Box 52)
  - Exchange Program/China, 1980-1982 (Box 52)
  - Classical Studies, 1980-1983 (Box 52)
  - Commencement, 1981-1983 (Box 52)
  - Comparative Literature, 1974-1983 (Box 53)
  - Computer Kamp-DUCK, 1981-1983 (Box 53)
  - Computer Science, 1980-1983 (Box 53)
  - Computerization of Languages Oriented Enterprises, COLOE, 1982-1983 (Box 53)
  - Continuing Education, 1980-1983 (Box 53)
  - Task Forces Cooperative Program, 1979-1980 (Box 53)
  - General Correspondence: A-C, 1974-1983 (Box 53)
  - General Correspondence: D-F, 1974-1983 (Box 54)
  - General Correspondence: G-I, 1974-1983 (Box 54)
  - General Correspondence: J-L, 1974-1983 (Box 54)
  - General Correspondence: M-O, 1974-1983 (Box 54)
  - General Correspondence: P-R, 1974-1983 (Box 54)
  - General Correspondence: S-T, 1974-1983 (Box 54)
  - General Correspondence: U-Z, 1974-1983 (Box 54)
  - Course Schedules, 1980-1983 (Box 54)
  - Curriculum Review Panels, 1979-1980 (Box 54)
  - Danforth Foundation, 1974-1978 (Box 54)
  - Dean's Council, 1981-1982 (Box 54)
  - Dean's Staff, 1980-1982 (Box 54)
  - Dean's Staff Minutes, 1980-1982 (Box 54)
  - Department Chairmen, 1980-1982 (Box 54)
  - Development, 1982-1983 (Box 54)
  - Development, 1970-1981 (Box 55)
  - Directors of Undergraduate Studies, 1980-1983 (Box 55)
  - Distinguished Professors, 1982 (Box 55)
  - Distinguished Professor Seminars, 1980-1981 (Box 55)
  - Drama, 1980-1982 (Box 55)
  - The Duke Endowment, 1977-1983 (Box 55)
  - Nominees: Duke Endowment Awards for Excellence in Teaching, 1977-1980 (Box 55)
  - Duke Endowment Leaves, 1979-1982 (Box 55)
  - Duke Endowment Leaves Applications, 1979-1980 (Box 55)
  - The Duke Experience: TCAS, 1984 (Box 55)
  - Duke Players, 1972-1975 (Box 55)
  - Dumont Lecture, 1981 (Box 55)
  - Economics, 1980-1983 (Box 55)
  - Economics Enrollment, 1979 (Box 56)
  - Edens Federation, 1975-1982 (Box 56)
  - Education, Program in, 1983 (Box 56)
  - Education, 1982 (Box 56)
  - Education Department, 1980-1981 (Box 56)
  - Educational Facilities Committee, 1979-1982 (Box 56)
  - Educational Policy and Program Special Committee, 1980 (Box 56)
  - Employee Services, 1982 (Box 56)
  - School of Engineering, 1977-1983 (Box 56)
  - English, 1980-1984 (Box 56)
  - Faculty Fellows, 1974-1982 (Box 56)
  - Faculty: General, 1981-1982 (Box 56)
  - Faculty: General, 1978-1980 (Box 57)
  - Faculty Handbook, 1978-1982 (Box 57)
  - Faculty Newsletter, 1980-1983 (Box 57)
  - Faculty-in-Residence, 1982-1983 (Box 57)
  - Faculty Salaries, 1980-1984 (Box 57)